A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA387b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- England, 1921-1978; 401; 74 box(es)
  - England - Nursing, 401.C
    - College of Nursing, London - Carpenter, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 146)
    - College of Nursing, London - Thompson, A. - (Travel Grant), 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 147)
    - St. George's Hospital - Powell, M. - (Travel Grant) (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 401.D
    - Agricultural Research Council - Russel - (Travel Grant), 1956 (Box 17, Folder 149)
    - Birkbeck College - Klug, A. - (Travel Grant), 1957-1959, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 150)
    - Birkbeck College - X-Ray Analysis, 1949-1952 (Box 17, Folder 151)
    - Boulter, D. - (Travel Grant), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 152)
    - Breiger, E. M. - Electron Microscopy, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 153)
    - Brimble, L. - (Travel Grant), 1955 (Box 17, Folder 154)
    - British Museum - Natural History - Reid, J., 1958-1964, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 155)
    - British Orinthologists Union - Symposium, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 156)
    - Broodhead, E. - (Travel Grant), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - Cockcroft, J. D. - (Travel Grant), 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 158)
    - Commonwealth Agricultural Bureau - Journals, 1962-1966 (Box 18, Folder 159)
    - Commonwealth Agricultural Bureau - Journals, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 160)
    - Commonwealth Agricultural Bureau - Nutrition, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 161)
    - Commonwealth Myscological Institute - Ainsworth, G. C., 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 162)
    - Commonwealth Myscological Institute - Botony, 1951-1954 (Box 18, Folder 163)
    - East Malling Research Station - Crosse, J. E. - (Travel Grant), 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 164)
    - East Malling Research Station - Pitcher, R. S., 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 165)
    - East Malling Research Station - Posnette, A. - (Travel Grant), 1956, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 166)
    - Franklin, R. - Physical Chemistry - (Travel Grant), 1956 (Box 18, Folder 167)
    - Gabor, Dennis - (Travel Grant), 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 168)
    - Goodwin, T. W. - (Travel Grant), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 169)
    - Honeyman, John - (Travel Grant), 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 170)
    - Hopwood, D. A. - (Travel Grant), 1960 (Box 19, Folder 171)
    - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Electron Microscope, 1958-1960, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 172)
    - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Mason, B. J. - (Travel Grant), 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 173)
    - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Water Research, 1952-1963 (Box 19, Folder 174)
    - Institute of Biology - Population Symposium, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 175)
    - John Innes Horticultural Institution - Potato Study, 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 176)
    - John Innes Institute, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 177)
    - Kalmus, H. - Genetics, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 178)
    - King's College - Electrophysiology, 1953-1957 (Box 19, Folder 179)
    - King's College - Embryology, 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 180)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1945-1948 (Box 20, Folder 181)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 182)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 183)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1951-1953 (Box 20, Folder 184)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 185)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 186)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 187)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 188)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 189)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 190)
    - King's College - Molecular Biology - (Reports) (Box 21, Folder 191)
    - Lister Institute of Preventive Medicine - Biochemistry, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 192)
    - Lister Institute of Preventive Medicine - Cinader, B. - (Travel Grant), 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    - Lister Institute of Preventive Medicine - Whelan, William - (Travel Grant), 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    - Lister School of Hygiene - Bertram, D. - (Travel Grant), 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 195)
    - London School of Hygiene - Sanders, F. - (Travel Grant), 1953 (Box 22, Folder 196)
    - London School of Hygiene - Tropical Nutrition, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 197)
    - London School of Hygiene - Tropical Nutrition, 1958-May 1959 (Box 22, Folder 198)
    - London School of Hygiene - Tropical Nutrition, 1959-1964 (Box 22, Folder 199)
    - Marine Biological Association, Plymouth - Laboratory, 1952-1954 (Box 22, Folder 200)
    - Marine Biological Association, Plymouth - Laboratory, 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder 201)
    - Marine Biological Association, Plymouth - Laboratory, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 202)
    - Marian, D. H. - Experimental Biology-Biochemistry - (Travel Grant), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 203)
    - McDonald, D. A. - (Travel Grant), 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 204)
    - National Institute for Research in Dairying - Cowie, A. - (Travel Grant), 1950-1952 (Box 23, Folder 205)
    - National Institute for Research in Dairying - Kon, S. - (Travel Grant), 1951-1953 (Box 23, Folder 206)
    - National Institute for Research in Dairying - Nutrition, 1956-1959 (Box 23, Folder 207)
    - National Institute for Research in Dairying - Physiology, 1956-1958, 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 208)
    - National Vegetable Research Station, 1958-1959 (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Oxford University - Acheson, R., 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 210)
    - Oxford University - Animal Population, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 211)
    - Oxford University - Elton, C., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 212)
    - Oxford University - Enzyme Biochemistry, 1946-1951 (Box 23, Folder 213)
    - Oxford University - Kittlewell, H., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 214)
    - Oxford University - Krebs, Hans, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 215)
    - Oxford University - Krebs, Hans, 1957-1963 (Box 24, Folder 216)
    - Oxford University - Microbiology, 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 217)
    - Oxford University - Microscopy, 1949-1956 (Box 24, Folder 218)
    - Oxford University - Organic Chemistry, 1956-1964 (Box 24, Folder 219)
    - Oxford University - Physical Chemistry, 1948-1950 (Box 24, Folder 220)
    - Oxford University - Stocken, Lloyd, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 221)
    - Oxford University - Woodford, E. K., 1953-1955 (Box 24, Folder 222)
    - Oxford University - Riley, R., 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 223)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Bowden, F. C., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 224)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - CO-2 Assimilation, 1957-1959, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 225)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Glynne, Mary - (Travel Grant), 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 226)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Gregory, P. - (Travel Grant), 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 227)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Jones, F. - (Travel Grant), 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 228)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Lapwood, D. - (Travel Grant), 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 229)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Protein Research, 1951, 1956-1965, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 230)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Statistics, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 231)
    - Rowley, Derrick - Bacteriology - (Travel Grant), 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 232)
    - Royal Cancer Hospital - Philips, D. - (Travel Grant) (Box 25, Folder 233)
    - Royal Cancer Hospital - Roe, Edna - (Travel Grant), 1951 (Box 25, Folder 234)
    - Royal Society, London - Crystallography Congress, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 235)
    - Rushton, William A. H. - (Travel Grant), 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 236)
    - St. Bartholomew's Hospital - Wormall, A., 1955 (Box 25, Folder 237)
    - St. Mary's Hospital Medical School - Proteins, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 238)
    - Simmonds, N. W. - Cytogenetics - (Travel Grant), 1959 (Box 25, Folder 239)
    - Smales, A. A. - Agriculture-Chemistry - (Travel Grant), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 240)
    - Smith, K. M. - (Travel Grant), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 241)
    - Society of Experimental Biology - Symposium, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - Society of Experimental Biology - Symposium, 1950-1952 (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - Society of Experimental Biology - Symposium, 1953-1957 (Box 26, Folder 244)
    - Society for General Microbiology - Symposium, 1952-1955 (Box 26, Folder 245)
    - Tait, James F. - (Travel Grant), 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 246)
    - University of Birmingham - Biochemistry, 1949-1954 (Box 26, Folder 247)
    - University of Birmingham - Biochemistry, 1955-1961 (Box 26, Folder 248)
    - University of Birmingham - Biochemistry - Peacocke, A. R., 1953-1959 (Box 26, Folder 249)
    - University of Birmingham - Hawkes, J., 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 250)
    - University of Birmingham - Lowenstein, Otto, 1952, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - University of Birmingham - Tarn, T. R., 1964, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - University of Birmingham - Molecular Biology (Box 27, Folder 253)
    - University of Birmingham - Sciences, 1958-1963 (Box 27, Folder 254)
    - University of Bristol - Anatomy, 1948-1956 (Box 27, Folder 255)
    - University of Bristol - Biochemistry, 1953-1956, 1958-1961 (Box 27, Folder 256)
    - University of Cambridge - Animal Behavior, 1951-1954 (Box 27, Folder 257)
    - University of Cambridge - Animal Behavior, 1956-1957, 1959-1964, 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 258)
    - University of Cambridge - Animal Reproduction, 1955-1960 (Box 27, Folder 259)
    - University of Cambridge - Animal Reproduction, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - University of Cambridge - Animal Reproduction, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 261)
    - University of Cambridge - Animal Reproduction, 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 262)
    - University of Cambridge - Beveridge, W., 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - University of Cambridge - Botany, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 264)
    - University of Cambridge - Colloid Science, 1947-1948 (Box 28, Folder 265)
    - University of Cambridge - Colloid Science, 1949-1952 (Box 28, Folder 266)
    - University of Cambridge - Colloid Science, 1954-1959 (Box 28, Folder 267)
    - University of Cambridge - Cosslett, V. E., 1951 (Box 28, Folder 268)
    - University of Cambridge - Cotes, P. Mary, 1950-1952 (Box 29, Folder 269)
    - University of Cambridge - Entomology, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 270)
    - University of Cambridge - Genetics, 1949-1951 (Box 29, Folder 271)
    - University of Cambridge - Ingram, Vernon, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 272)
    - University of Cambridge - Keynes, R. D., 1958 (Box 29, Folder 273)
    - University of Cambridge - Massey, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 274)
    - University of Cambridge - Molecular Biology, 1949-1951 (Box 29, Folder 275)
    - University of Cambridge - Organic Chemistry, 1947-1950 (Box 29, Folder 276)
    - University of Cambridge - Organic Chemistry, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 277)
    - University of Cambridge - Organic Chemistry, 1953-1955 (Box 29, Folder 278)
    - University of Cambridge - Organic Chemistry, 1956-1966 (Box 29, Folder 279)
    - University of Cambridge - Smith, C., 1952-1953 (Box 29, Folder 280)
    - University of Cambridge - Sykes, 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 281)
    - University College - Biochemistry - Young, 1947-1950 (Box 30, Folder 282)
    - University College - Botany, 1953-1956, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 283)
    - University College - Botany - Fowden, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 284)
    - University College - Evans, I., 1954-1956 (Box 30, Folder 285)
    - University College - Enzyme Chemistry, 1956-1960 (Box 30, Folder 286)
    - University College - Hill, A., 1953-1954 (Box 30, Folder 287)
    - University College - Zoology, 1953-1956, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 288)
    - University College, Nottingham - Biochemistry, 1949-1953 (Box 30, Folder 289)
    - University College, Nottingham - Matty, A. - (Travel Grant), 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 290)
    - University of Durham - Ellenby, C., 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 291)
    - University of Durham - Protein Chemistry, 1955-1956, 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 292)
    - University of Durham - Radiation Studies, 1949, 1951-1960 (Box 31, Folder 293)
    - University Grants Committee - Murray, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 294)
    - University of Leeds - Beard, D. S., 1950 (Box 31, Folder 295)
    - University of Leeds - Microscopy, 1951-1958, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 296)
    - University of Leeds - Microscopy - Manton, 1953-1955 (Box 31, Folder 297)
    - University of Leeds - Radiation Chemistry, 1952-1955, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 298)
    - University of Leeds - X-Ray Crytallography (Box 31, Folder 299)
    - University of Liverpool - Biochemistry, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 300)
    - University of Liverpool - Burges, Herman, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 301)
    - University of Liverpool - Endocrinology Symposium, 1953-1956 (Box 31, Folder 302)
    - University of Liverpool - Sheppard, P., 1959 (Box 32, Folder 303)
    - University of London - Plant Physiology, 1958-1960, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 304)
    - University of Manchester - Harland, S. C., 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 305)
    - University of Manchester - Plant Physiology, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 306)
    - University of Reading - Agricultural Conference, 1966-1967 (July) (Box 32, Folder 307)
    - University of Reading - Agricultural Conference, 1967 (August-December) (Box 32, Folder 308)
    - University of Reading - Agricultural Conference, 1967 (June-July) (Box 32, Folder 309)
    - University of Reading - Agricultural Conference, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 310)
    - University of Reading - Agricultural Conference, 1969 (Jan-March) (Box 32, Folder 311)
    - University of Reading - Agricultural Conference, 1969 (April-December) (Box 33, Folder 312)
    - University of Reading - Agricultural Conference, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 313)
    - University of Sheffield - Microbiology, 1954-1958, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 314)
    - University of Southampton - Ingram, J. E., 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 315)
    - Van Heynengen, W. E. - (Travel Grant), 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 316)
    - Willmer, E. Neville - (Travel Grant), 1956 (Box 33, Folder 317)
    - Worthington, E. B. - (Travel Grant), 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 318)
    - Wye College - Plant Growth, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 319)
    - Wye College - Plant Pathology, 1959-1963 (Box 33, Folder 320)
    - Wye College - Entomology, 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 321)
    - Wye College - Skillbeck, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 322)
    - Wye College - Wain, R. L., 1961-1962, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 323)
  - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 401.E
    - British Medical Research Council, 1921-1923 (Box 34, Folder 324)
    - British Medical Research Council, 1924-1926 (Box 34, Folder 325)
    - Institute of Civil Engineers, 1952-1954 (Box 34, Folder 326)
    - Institute of Civil Engineers, 1955-1961 (Box 34, Folder 327)
  - England - Health Services, 401.K
    - England - Health Services, 1951-1955 (Box 34, Folder 328)
    - Ackers, G. L. (Travel Grant), 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 329)
    - University of Durham, 1954-1957 (Box 34, Folder 330)
    - University of Manchester - Cornish, 1954-1956 (Box 34, Folder 331)
  - England - Public Health Education, 401.L
    - London School of Hygiene - Experimental Area, 1950-1955 (Box 35, Folder 332)
  - England - Humanities and Arts, 401.R
    - Adams, W. (Travel Grant), 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 333)
      For stack material, see box 74
    - Association of Special Libraries and Information Bureaus - Union Catalogue, 1947-1952 (Box 35, Folder 334)
    - Association of Special Libraries and Information Bureaus - Union Catalogue, 1944-1946 (Box 35, Folder 335)
    - Association of Special Libraries and Information Bureaus - Union Catalogue, 1947-1952 (Box 35, Folder 336)
    - Association of Special Libraries and Information Bureaus - Union Catalogue, 1953-1958 (Box 35, Folder 337)
    - Ayrton, Michael (Travel Grant), 1954-1955 (Box 35, Folder 338)
    - British Academy - Humanities, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 339)
    - British Academy - Humanities, 1959-1962 (Box 36, Folder 340)
    - Brock, Michael (Travel Grant), 1959-1960, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 341)
    - Dortington Hall - Theatre School, 1947-1950 (Box 36, Folder 342)
    - Drama - Davis, A., 1950-1951 (Box 36, Folder 343)
    - Hulin, Peter (Travel Grant), 1961, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 344)
    - Jay, Peter (Travel Grant), 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 345)
    - London School of Economics and Political Science - Smith, Marion, 1953-1954 (Box 37, Folder 346)
    - London School of Economics and Political Science - Stirling, A. Paul, 1952-1955 (Box 37, Folder 347)
    - London School of Oriental Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 37, Folder 348)
    - London School of Oriental Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 349)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Basham, A. L., 1962 (Box 37, Folder 350)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Beasley, W. G., 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 351)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Indian History (Singh), 1953, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 352)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Islamic Art, 1956-1960 (Box 37, Folder 353)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Islam-Muslim Atlas, 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 354)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Middle Eastern Historical Writing, 1956-1959 (Box 38, Folder 355)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Philips, C. H., 1954-1957 (Box 38, Folder 356)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - South Asia Historical Writing, 1953-1957 (Box 38, Folder 357)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - South Asia Historical Writing, 1958-1961 (Box 38, Folder 358)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - South Asia Historical Writing, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 359)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - South Asia Historical Writing - (Supplementary Material) (Box 39, Folder 360)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - South Asia Source Guide, 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 361)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Tibetan Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 362)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Tibetan Studies, 1959, 1962-1966 (Box 39, Folder 363)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Turkish Contemporary Literature, 1962-1966 (Box 39, Folder 364)
    - London School of Oriental Studies - Van der Sprenkel, 1949-1950 (Box 40, Folder 365)
    - Myers, Adolph, 1952-1953 (Box 40, Folder 366)
    - Oxford University - Allen, H. C., 1952-1955 (Box 40, Folder 367)
    - Oxford University - American Studies, 1951-1958 (Box 40, Folder 368)
    - Oxford University - American Studies - Reports (Box 40, Folder 369)
    - Oxford University - American Studies - Beloff, 1946-1947 (Box 40, Folder 370)
    - Oxford University - American Studies, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 371)
    - Oxford University - American Studies - Beloff, 1949-1950, 1952-1955 (Box 40, Folder 372)
    - Oxford University - Anscombe, Gertrude E. M. - Philosophy, 1951-1958 (Box 41, Folder 373)
    - Oxford University - Briggs, Asa - Urban History, 1951-1954 (Box 41, Folder 374)
    - Oxford University - Clark, Sir George N. - (Travel Grant), 1951-1954 (Box 41, Folder 375)
    - Oxford University - European Studies, 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 376)
    - Oxford University - European Studies, 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 377)
    - Oxford University - European Studies, 1959-1965 (Box 41, Folder 378)
    - Oxford University - European Studies - Supplementary Material (Box 42, Folder 379)
    - Oxford University - European Studies - Supplementary Material (Box 42, Folder 380)
    - Oxford University - Gopal, S. - Contemporary Indian History, 1964-1967 (Box 42, Folder 381)
    - Oxford University - Greg, W. W., 1946-1950 (Box 42, Folder 382)
    - Oxford University - Kot, Stanislas, 1953-September 1955 (Box 42, Folder 383)
    - Oxford University - Kot, Stanislas, October 1955-1960 (Box 42, Folder 384)
    - Oxford University - Near Eastern Studies - Stoakes, Frank, 1955-1958 (Box 42, Folder 385)
    - Oxford University - Ogilvie, Lady Mary, 1954-1956 (Box 43, Folder 386)
    - Oxford University - Patterson, Colin H., 1949-1953 (Box 43, Folder 387)
    - Oxford University - Patterson, Colin H. - Medical Examination (Box 43, Folder 388)
    - Oxford University - Patterson, David - (Brenner, Joseph H.), 1958-1961 (Box 43, Folder 389)
    - Oxford University - Wrenn, C. L. - (Phonetics and Linguistics), 1949-1950, 1952-1953, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 390)
    - Oxford University - Rowse, A. L., 1950-1952 (Box 43, Folder 391)
    - Oxford University Press - Creswell, K. A. C. - Muslim Architecture, 1951-1955 (Box 43, Folder 392)
    - Oxford University Press Credwell, K. A. C. "A Bibliography of Painting in Islam" Reports/Item (Box 43, Folder 393)
    - Oxford University Press - Jacobsthal, Paul, 1944-1951, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 394)
    - Oxford University Press - Soviet History, 1945-1950, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 395)
    - Peel, Albert, 1940-1946, 1948, 1951, 1957, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 396)
    - Religious Drama Society, 1953-1956 (Box 44, Folder 397)
    - Religious Drama Society, 1957-1962 (Box 44, Folder 398)
    - Religious Drama Society - Supplementary Material, 1951, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 399)
    - Religious Drama Society - Supplementary Material, 1951-1961 (Box 44, Folder 400)
    - Royal Asiatic Society, London - Cronin, Vincent, 1957-1959 (Box 45, Folder 401)
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs - Sherrard, Philip O. A., 1954-1959 (Box 45, Folder 402)
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1951-May 1952 (Box 45, Folder 403)
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs - Toynbee, Arnold J., June 1952-August 1955 (Box 45, Folder 404)
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs - Toynbee, Arnold J., October 1955-1958 (Box 45, Folder 405)
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs - World History - Barraclough, Geoffrey, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 406)
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs - World History, 1961-1966 (Box 46, Folder 407)
    - Saint Catherine's College - Medieval History, 1960-1962 (Box 46, Folder 408)
    - Salop County Council - Community Arts, 1953-1954 (Box 46, Folder 409)
    - Sullivan, Donovan M., 1959-1961 (Box 46, Folder 410)
    - University of Birmingham - American Studies - Hawgood, John A., 1954 (Box 46, Folder 411)
    - University of Birmingham - Elizabethan Literature, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 412)
    - University of Birmingham - Elizabethan Literature, 1948, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 413)
    - University of Birmingham - Elizabethan Literature, 1954-1956 (Box 46, Folder 414)
    - University of Birmingham - Literary Awards, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 415)
    - University of Birmingham - Literary Awards, 1947-1949 (Box 47, Folder 416)
    - University of Birmingham - Literary Awards, 1947-1951, 1953-1954, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 417)
    - University of Birmingham - Literary Awards - Reports (Box 47, Folder 418)
    - University of Bristol - Drama, 1942, 1949-1963 (Box 47, Folder 419-423)
    - University of Bristol - Far Eastern Studies, 1948-1951, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 424)
    - University of Cambridge - African History Journal, 1958-1966 (Box 48, Folder 425)
    - University of Cambridge - American Studies - Thistlethwaite, Frank, 1949-1950, 1952-1956 (Box 48, Folder 426)
    - University of Cambridge - American Studies Conference, 1953-1956 (Box 48, Folder 427)
    - University of Cambridge - American Studies Conference - Reports, 1952-1955; 3 Items (Box 48, Folder 428)
    - University of Cambridge - Chinese Union List, 1952-1956 (Box 48, Folder 429)
    - University of Cambridge - Elliott, John H. - (Latin American Studies), 1962-1964 (Box 48, Folder 430)
    - University of Cambridge - Leavis, F. R., 1945-1955 (Box 49, Folder 431)
    - University of Cambridge - Moore Papers - (Philosophy), 1959-1963 (Box 49, Folder 432)